Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- Chicago Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Federation news, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Author: Federation news (Chicago Federation of Labor)
  - Item 2: Handbook of the Chicago Industrial Exhibit, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Author: Chicago (Ill.). Industrial Exhibit, 1907
  - Item 3: Independent Labor Party platform, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Author: Chicago Federation of Labor and Industrial Union Council
  - Item 4: Labor-welfare in our community, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Legal opinion: Women's Compensation Act, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: newspapers and miscellaneous letters, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The official labor union directory, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Central Labor Union, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Official Souvenir and Programme, Central Labor Union and Building Trades' Council of Buffalo, N.Y., Labor Day, Monday, September 3d, 1894., Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Author: Buffalo Central Labor Union
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: newspaper clippings, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Souvenir Program, 50th Anniversary of the Binghamton Central Labor Union and 21st Annual Convention of Union Label Trades Department, State of New York., 1947; Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Trade and Labor Assembly of Chicago, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of T. J. Morgan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Author: Trade and Labor Assembly of Chicago
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor-management: on Columbia River Project, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Author: Oscar G. Harbak
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: newspaper clippings, Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Lest we forget, Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Elmira labor review, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Amherst College, Holyoke Central Labor Union, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: List of classes offered, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Author: Amherst College, Holyoke Central Labor Union
- Central Labor Union, Ithaca, NY, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Its organization, administration and functions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Author: Central Labor Union, Ithaca, NY
    Notes: Copy of a speech on this topic
  - Item 2: Labor Advisory Committee reports progressCommunity Chest Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Author: Labor Advisory Committee of the Community Chest
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Ithaca union labor review, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Kenosha union label directory and purchasing guide, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Ithaca journal., Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles County Central Labor Council., Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Golden anniversary, 1901-1951, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Author: Los Angeles County Central Labor Council.
- Mercer County Workers Education Council, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Workers' Education, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Author: Mercer County Workers Education Council
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Designed for Export?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee labor press., Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The decline of the medical profession in the public esteem., Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Author: Milwaukee labor press.
    Notes: Based on a series of 25 articles, "The tarnished record of the American Medical Association," as originally appearing in the Milwaukee labor press.
- Federated Trades Council, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Record of proceedings, 1950-1958 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Author: Federated Trades Council
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: pamphlet, Publication (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Author: Minneapolis (AFL)
    Notes: Lost its cover, title page and some pages from the back.
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor's news, 1931; Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.20:no.4,7-16, (1931) and miscellaneous issues that are very brittle.
- Eastern Pennsylvania Central Labor Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Directory, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Author: Central Federated Union of New York
  - Item 2: miscellaneous papers - "Don't give consumption to others ", and a "Financial report for six months ending June 30th, 1901", Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Author: Eastern Pennsylvania Central Labor Unions
- Eastern Pennsylvania Central Labor Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fifth Educational Institute conference (1950), Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Notes: Two invitations to conferences and a program
  - Item 2: Minutes (1948-1952) (Box 31, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: $10,475 pledged by labor..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Notes: Newspaper clippings.
  - Item 2: $5,000 libel levy on union..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: City labor bodies prepare to unite, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Mayor leads anti-seaway drive, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Morality splits AFL, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: New traffic move in garment center, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Progress is made toward labor act, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Smooth adjustment predicted at falls, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Labor to get part in New York fund, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Coliseum unions in accord on pact, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Central Labor Union of Philadelphia and Vicinity, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual directory and magazine, 1936; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Author: Central Labor Union of Philadelphia and Vicinity
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Philadelphia Labor-Medical Story, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Author: American Federation of Labor. Medical Service Plan of Philadelphia.
  - Item 2: Your Health - Serial/periodical, not catalogedthree issues, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: A.F. of L. Medical Center, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: By-laws, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: souvenir pamphlet from opening ceremonies at the opening of the Medical Center, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Philadelphia textile industry Labor's viewpoint, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Pittsburgh Labor Education Council, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A conference on objectives of the labor movement public issues facing labor in 1952: Hotel Sheraton, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, September 20, 1952, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Author: Pittsburgh Labor Education Council
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: AFL urges action here, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: CIO organizing war on hoarding and profiteering..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Illustrated history of the Central Trades and Labor Council, Rochester, N.Y., 1927; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Author: Emanuel Koveleski
    Notes: Also New York State Federation of Labor and showing statistical data anent the march of Union Organized Labor along the Highway of Time during the past 75 years
  - Item 4: Labor Men will attend dinner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Labor news, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Author: Labor news (Rochester, N.Y.)
  - Item 6: Panel to discuss public relations for labor unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: State labor board hamstrings unions..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Union label drive mapped by AFL, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Unions close Cornell talks, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: What's the Matter with Reading, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: 14 unions seek boosts, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: 3 locals linked to CIO..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: AFL council to back arbitration proposal, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: AFL gets appeal for defense..., Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: AFL seeks new members, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Truth about the street car trouble, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Labor Council., Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Official bulletin - San Francisco Labor Council, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Author: San Francisco Labor Council.
    Notes: Includes Official minutes of San Francisco Labor Council. Issues are not complete but, have a few from each yr/mo in holdings
- San Francisco Employers Council., Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Author: San Francisco Employers Council.
    Notes: 1957 June
  - Item 2: Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1956 February
  - Item 3: Registration bulletin no.1, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The battle of America, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Men on the job, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Notes: Pamphlet advertising a 35mm slide film study of tolerance
  - Item 2: 70th Annual Convention, Sept. 17, 1951, San Francisco, California", Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Notes: Souvenir program
  - Item 3: Let's look behind the oratory: what are the records of the two parties on the issues that affect your well-being?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: San Francisco Labor Council scrutinizes group insurance, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Author: Norbert Cronin
  - Item 5: The San Francisco Labor Council survey: Labor plans for health. A study of health and welfare plans under collective bargaining among unions affiliated with the San Francisco Labor Council., 1952; Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Author: E. Richard Weinerman
- San Francisco Labor Council., Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Official bulletin - San Francisco Labor Council., Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Schenectady Labor Temple Association, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Directory, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Author: Schenectady Labor Temple Association
    Notes: Affiliated with the Schenectady Federation of Labor, New York State Federation of Labor, American Federation of Labor. Mainly an advertisement directory
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: City AFL unit to hear talk by Hanover, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Federation of Labor supports construction of S-G High School, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Stratton spurns Mayor's pleas to use influence, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The right-to-work laws: speech to management and labor at Catholic Seamen's Club Seattle Washington February 18, 1955, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Author: Jerome L. Toner
  - Item 2: The Seattle General Strike: an account of what happened in Seattle, and especially in the Seattle labor movement during the General Strike, February 6 to 11, 1919, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Central Trades and Labor Assembly of Syracuse and Vicinity, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Official directory, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Author: Central Trades and Labor Assembly of Syracuse and Vicinity
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: End to Oak Ridge Strike seen likely on May 31, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Industry Day for teachers is Thursday, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Most men continue atomic plant strike, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Rent control removal will be aired, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Wildcat walkout of 700 laborers puzzles authorities at Oak Ridge, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Tennessee Valley Authority, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Manual for cooperative committee members, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Author: Tennessee Valley Authority. Central Joint Cooperative Committee
  - Item 2: Teamwork, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Troy Labor Federation to meet Jan. 18, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Utica Trades Assembly, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Hours of Labor' bill before the NY Senate and Assembly, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Author: Utica Trades Assembly
    Notes: Photocopy of a proposed bill.
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: picture of 'AFL effective speaking graduates, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: WGAT returns to air today without Davies, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: AFL backs drive here for workshop, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Labor group reelects all officers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Picture of 'Watertown Labor Leaders', Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The CIO, what it is and how it came to be: a brief history of the Committee for Industrial Organization, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Protect the Wagner Act!: Full appropriation to the National Labor Relations Board!: No prying investigations into the Board!, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Why the Wagner Act should not be amended, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Your rights under the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.) Legal Dept.
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Industrial unionism, Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: How the rubber workers won, Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Radio address - "Industrial Democracy in steel", Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Author: John Llewellyn Lewis
  - Item 3: Statement' to the Officers and Members of State Federation of Labor about union activities and general to catalog, Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Why the C.I.O., Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Author: Alfred Baker Lewis
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: An open letter to the membership of the I.L.A. from the C.I.O., Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: one page. Restricted?
  - Item 2: John Lewis - Dictator, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: Photocopy of some pages torn from a publication
  - Item 3: The Palooka, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: Flyer from Committee for Industrial Organization
  - Item 4: Welcome to the C.I.O., Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: Photocopy of a 'message to the members of New Local Industrial Uniosn' Restricted?
  - Item 5: Building America, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Labor and the nation, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: letter from Committee for Industrial Organization to all local Industrial Unions, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Notes: regarding unemployment and operations slowdown - brief
  - Item 8: The C.I.O. and the farmers, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The C-I-O and the white collar worker, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The program of the C.I.O., Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Call for the Constitutional Convention, 1938; Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Notes: opening speech made on Oct. 6, 1938
  - Item 2: Aid for the unemployed: and how to get it, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Labor's program for better housing, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Committee on Housing
  - Item 4: Report of Chairman John L. Lewis to the first constitutional convention of the CIO, Pittsburgh, Pa., November 14, 1938., Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: For the nation's security, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations. Dept. of Education and Research.
  - Item 2: Social Security from the C.I.O. Committee on Social Security June 6, 1938, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Notes: Two reports
  - Item 3: The church speaks out for labor, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: I belong here, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Richard Cushing
  - Item 2: Invocation and address by most Rev. Edward F. Hoban, STD, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations
    Notes: for release upon delivery Monday, October 31, 1949
  - Item 3: The path we must follow leads neither to right nor left, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: William O. Douglas
  - Item 4: Time to get angry: a speech, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: James B.Carey
  - Item 5: We shall march together: two statements, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
- Office of the U.S. Special Representative in Europe, Paris, France, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Riffe brings two decades of unionism to No. 2 CIO job, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Author: Office of the U.S. Special Representative in Europe, Paris, France
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 25% industry wage rise is backed in CIO report, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 7 to 10% pay rises held industry top, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Bowles is derided for union-aid plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Britons are 'put hep' to our slang, signboards, saloons by NAM aide, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: C.I.O. '47 pay demands likely to be flexible, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: C.I.O. asserts industry can raise pay 30%, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: C.I.O. begins, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: C.I.O. charged with anti-union act by ex-aid, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: C.I.O. in south, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: C.I.O. in south faces obstacle in racial issue, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: C.I.O. is seen starting pay drive in increasingly hostile climate, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: C.I.O. restricts units in giving aid to pro-reds, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: C.I.O.-A.F. of L. merger viewed as unlikely now, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: C.I.O.'s 1947 pay demands, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: C.M.U. leaders vote to dissolve organization, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Carey regards CIO no longer in WFTU, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: CIO asks wage rises, reduction in profits, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: CIO big three meet Monday on '47 pay plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: CIO head says Taft 'retreats' on law, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: CIO hits welfare plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: CIO ready to take part of AFL plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: CIO rejects move to 'capture' party, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: CIO steps up fight on pro-communists, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: CIO TUC and Dutch walk out of WFTU, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: CIO urged to form one marine union, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Coming C.I.O. decisions viewed as fraught with peril for public, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Gate-to-gate pay gains as CIO issue, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Insists U.S. study CIO profit report, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Leftists assail C.I.O. policy in Taft Act fight, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Murray agrees to talk over A.F.L. unity bid, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Murray demands rise in pay rates, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Murray in battle for store unions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Murray letter asking labor unity, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Murray offers to meet green to outlaw jurisdictional strike, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Murray outlines 'labor's responsibilities', Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: N.A.M. rebuts C.I.O. excessive profit charge, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: N.A.M. says nonsense to C.I.O. on pay, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Nathan expects '47 pay rise at current prices, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Pay rise push on 25% level, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Ship lines await hiring-hall action, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 41: Southern drive of C.I.O. is far short of goal, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 42: Southern paper brings news of C.I.O. into open, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: Statute drafted for a curb on PAC, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 44: Taft Act assailed in Senate report, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Today and tomorrow, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 46: US Chamber replies to C.I.O. on wage rises, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Sea labor to seek cadet training cut, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: SEA unions of East ask negotiations, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: U.S. chamber calls on labor to drop 4th-round demands, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Van Bittner dies - Labor Leader, 64, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: 12 unions warn brewers against strike-breaking, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: 2 ship transfers protested by CIO, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Bland bill upheld by shipping group, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: CIO aide forecasts ship strike June 15, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: CIO asks U.S. fight on rise in idleness, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: CIO assails Taft on pact, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: CIO battles shift of ships to Italy, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: CIO calls wood bill worse that Taft Act, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: CIO Chiefs censure leftist minority, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)